<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidPayPalWebSdkIntegrationExample</string>
    <string name="action_shopping_cart">Shopping Cart</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="shopping_cart_fragment_label">Cart Details</string>
    <string name="catalog_fragment_label">Catalog</string>
    <string name="checkoutPayPalSpb">PayPal Checkout SPB</string>
    <string name="checkoutPayPalApi">PayPal Checkout API</string>
    <string name="productCatalogButtonLabel">Product Catalog</string>
    <string name="closeBtnLabel">Close</string>
    <string name="paymentCompletionSuccess">Your payment is successfully completed.</string>
    <string name="paymentCompletionSuccessPayPalOrderId">PayPal Order ID =</string>
    <string name="payPalOrderDetailsLoading">Fetch PayPal Order Details from your REST API and display the necessary information to the buyer</string>

    <string name="shopping_cart_page_description">
        The shopping cart page should provide a clear and organized summary of all items selected
        for purchase. At the top, it should display a concise overview of the total number of
        items and the overall cost, including any applicable taxes and shipping fees.
        Each product in the cart should be listed with a thumbnail image, brief description,
        quantity selector, and individual price. Users should have the ability to easily update
        quantities or remove items. The page should also feature options to apply discount codes
        or gift cards and provide a detailed breakdown of costs. Prominent buttons for proceeding
        to checkout and continuing shopping should be readily accessible. Additionally, the cart
        page should offer an option to save items for later, ensuring a smooth transition between
        shopping and checkout while enhancing the overall user experience.
    </string>

    <string name="catalog_page_description">
        This is an example catalog page.
        The catalog page of a your mobile app should offer a seamless and engaging shopping experience.
        At the top, it should feature a search bar for easy product or category lookup, alongside filter
        and sort options to refine search results by attributes such as price, popularity,
        or new arrivals. The page should prominently display product categories with intuitive icons
        or images, and showcase featured products through high-quality visuals and brief descriptions.
        Users should be able to view products in a grid or list format, with options for quick previews
        and detailed views. Additional elements include promotional banners for special offers,
        user reviews and ratings to guide purchase decisions, and easy access to the cart and
        wishlist. To enhance usability, the page should support personalization features,
        such as product recommendations, and include accessibility options like text size adjustment
        and high contrast mode. Interactive features like product zoom and 360-degree views can
        further enrich the user experience.
    </string>
</resources>